Please like us on twitter!
Hello, I'm Kakihara and I'm here to tell you that I will be throwing out the first pitch at the Meiji Jingu Baseball Stadium today!
It's my first time to throw out the first pitch, but some of our members have done it before.
I met with everyone yesterday, and first of all, Shio-chan told me that she's going to throw out the first pitch tomorrow and that she's cheering for me, so I'll be able to reach them without any problems.
Then Yan-chan and Saya also encouraged me by saying that they could reach the first pitch and that I would be fine.
I'm hoping that I can help them get off to a good start by making a good decision today.
So I'm going to go to pitching practice today.
Good afternoon.
Hi, I'm Saisnil.
I'm Saisnil.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Kakihara from Nogizaka46
Nice to meet you, Nogizaka46
Are you pitching today?
Yes!
OK
So, which one of us is going to win?
OK!
Baseball?
Backhand.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Aah!
Whoa!
Shrillo style!
It's called a windup.
Yes!
Put some power into it.
Oh, I see.
It can be used.
Oh!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Before.
Forward.
Yes, sir.
I'll be right behind you.
Ah!
I'm going to flip you in half.
Okay.
All right.
whoa!
Strike.
Nice.
One more time.
Strike out.
Oh!
Yeah!
LOL!
Wow, you're on the air.
Is that OK?
Yes, sir.
Thank you. Mini-mini strike ball.
You can really come in for strikes, can't you?
Wow.
Are you a little nervous?
I'm a little nervous.
What?
I'm fine.
Okay?
You're already practicing.
I'm fine.
Yeah, I'm good.
Thank you.
Spice eater.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
I'm throwing in the take.
I can't do two of the same trick.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
Yes, I've just finished express practice.
I even put my hair up for the show.
I put it in a ponytail.
I'm really psyched about it.
I'm ready to go.
I'm just waiting for the call
I'm just waiting to be called.
I usually stand on stage at a live concert
I usually stand on the stage and look at you all.
I've only been able to look around at the scenery.
so when I saw the Meiji Jingu Baseball Stadium for the first time
When I saw the Meiji Jingu Baseball Stadium
I thought this is what Meiji Jingu Baseball Stadium really is.
It's a place that has always taken care of me
I'd like to repay the kindness even a little bit.
I'd like to put a few strikes in.
I'll do my best to reach it.
That's great!
There's also meat sushi!
Looks delicious!
Wow!
I'm lost
Oh!
What?
Shaq?
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, sir.
That's... interesting.
I got it from my dad. He told me about it.
It's your father's.
Call me.
That's a first.
How's that? Can you hear me?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm, uh...
I'm serious.
Wait.
Today's speaker is Haruka Makino from Baseball High School 46.
Please give a big round of applause.
Baseball High School 46, tonight, you have the honor of being unleashed by my champion,
I hope you have a wonderful rest.
March 1, 1997, by the Tokyo Metropolitan Earthquake
Tokyo Metropolitan Earthquake Caused by Tokyo Metropolitan Earthquake Caused by Tokyo Metropolitan Earthquake Caused by Tokyo Metropolitan Earthquake Caused by Tokyo Metropolitan Earthquake
Wow!
You chewed!
You got it! I got it!
I just got back from the first pitch!
I was so nervous, really nervous.
I was already back-to-back.
I was so nervous until I stood on the mound.
Tsubaki-kun and Tsubaki-chan were so cute.
They made me feel relaxed and at ease.
I was thinking, "What if I miss, what if I throw it in the wrong place?
I was worried about what would happen if I missed it or threw it in a strange place, but it arrived safely with no problem.
I'm glad.
I also received this ball and the commemorative ball
I'd like to display it in my house as a treasured memory.
My part in the project is over.
I will go home with the infection.
Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to our channel.
[ED]